[AI Models

](https://thehive.ai/privacy)

[Solutions

](https://thehive.ai/privacy)

[Company

](https://thehive.ai/privacy)

#### Understand

Classify and detect content attributes.

#### Search

Search web content and custom datasets.

#### Generate

Generate images and text from prompts.

[Visual Moderation

Best-in-class moderation for images, videos, GIFs, and livestreams](https://hivemoderation.com/visual-moderation)

[Text Moderation

Moderate text and text in images with best-in-class deep learning models](https://hivemoderation.com/text-moderation)

[Audio Moderation

Real-time speech and sound moderation in audioReal-time speech and sound  
moderation in audio](https://hivemoderation.com/audio-moderation)

[CSAM Detection

Integrate Thorn's CSAM detection technology into moderation workflows](https://thehive.ai/apis/csam-detection)

[Contextual Scene Classification

Identify common objects, settings, and event types within videos and images](https://thehive.ai/apis/contextual-scene-classification)

[OCR

Extract emojis and text in 15+ languages from videos and images](https://thehive.ai/apis/ocr)

[Speech-to-Text

Transcribe audio in real-time across multiple languagesTranscribe audio in real-time across  
multiple languages](https://thehive.ai/apis/speech-to-text)

[Demographic

Identify demographic attributes within videos and images](https://thehive.ai/apis/demographic)

[Logo & Logo Location

Identify thousands of logos and common logo locations within videos and images](https://thehive.ai/apis/logo-detection)

[Translation

Translate text in real-time across  
multiple languagesTranslate text in real-time across  
multiple languages](https://thehive.ai/apis/translation)

[AI-Generated Content Classification

Identify AI-generated or modified images and text](https://thehive.ai/apis/ai-generated-content-classification)

Platform[AutoML

Build and deploy deep learning models for custom use cases](https://thehive.ai/solutions/auto-ml)

[Reverse Image Search

Find copies and variants of content against billions of public web images](https://thehive.ai/apis/reverse-image-search)

[Custom Search

Find copies and variants of content within a configurable media library](https://thehive.ai/apis/custom-search)

[Media Search

Find copies and variants of movies, TV shows, and broadcasts](https://thehive.ai/apis/media-search)

[NFT Search

Verify NFT uniqueness against millions of assets on major blockchains](https://thehive.ai/apis/nft-search)

[Contextual Search

Natural language search on large  
image sets](https://thehive.ai/apis/contextual-search)

[Celebrity Recognition

Identify tens of thousands of well-known public figures](https://thehive.ai/apis/celebrity-recognition)

[Likeness Detection

Identifies popular characters or artworks in visuals across IP domains](https://thehive.ai/apis/likeness-detection)

[Image Generation

Generate images using text prompts](https://thehive.ai/apis/image-generation)

[Multimodal Language Model

Generate descriptions and ask questions about image and video details](https://thehive.ai/apis/multimodal-language-model)

[Text Generation

Generate high-quality writing for marketing copy, programming, and more](https://thehive.ai/apis/text-generation)

[Video Generation

Generate videos using text prompts](https://thehive.ai/apis/video-generation)

#### Technology & Digital Platforms

Solutions for moderating content of all forms, ensuring proprietary content stays on your platform, and more.

#### Sports, Media, & Marketing

Solutions for measuring sponsorships, monitoring cross-platform advertising, and unlocking premium ad inventory.

By Audience

[For NFT Platforms

Protect creators and collectors from scams and fraud](https://thehive.ai/solutions/nft-platforms)[For Marketplaces

Verify listings, enforce digital ownership, and moderate user interactions](https://thehive.ai/solutions/marketplaces)

[For Dating Apps

Elevate user experience with better moderation and user verification](https://thehive.ai/solutions/dating-apps)[For Online Communities

Screen user-generated visual, text, and audio content in real-time](https://thehive.ai/solutions/online-communities)

By Application

[Moderation Dashboard

Streamline moderation workflows with our no-code Moderation Dashboard](https://hivemoderation.com/dashboard)[Content Moderation

Protect your community with real-time moderation of video, image, text, and audioProtect your community with real-time moderation of video, image, text,  
and audio](https://hivemoderation.com/)[AutoML

Build and deploy deep learning models for custom use cases](https://thehive.ai/solutions/auto-ml)

By Audience

[For Brands

Measure and manage cross-platform advertising and sponsorships](https://thehive.ai/solutions/brands)[For Publishers

Efficiently and effectively monetize advertising and sponsorship inventory](https://thehive.ai/solutions/publishers)

[For Agencies

Measure and manage cross-platform advertising and sponsorships](https://thehive.ai/solutions/agencies)[For Teams and Leagues

Monetize sponsorship asset inventory](https://thehive.ai/solutions/teams-and-leagues)

By Application

[Sponsorship Intelligence

Cross-platform sponsorship measurement platform, powered by Hive's AI](https://thehive.ai/solutions/sponsorship-intelligence)[Ad Intelligence

Analyze cross-platform ad intelligence in our Mensio platform](https://thehive.ai/solutions/ad-intelligence)[Context-Based Ad Targeting

Capitalize on ad inventory with contextual targeting and brand safety analysis](https://thehive.ai/solutions/context-based-ad-targeting)

Hive AI
=======

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 26, 2023.

#### Privacy Policy - Highlights

When you use or interact with our website or our content tagging and/or labeling services, artificial intelligence (AI)-based classification services, mobile applications and other related services (each a “Service”), we and third parties may obtain certain information about you. In this Highlights section, we provide an overview of our privacy practices related to the Services. Please review our full Privacy Policy below for a detailed explanation of our practices.

###### What Information We Obtain

* Information you provide when you use the Services, including when you sign up for communications, purchase products or services, create an account or register through the Services. This may include your contact, payment or demographic information.

* Information you submit when you choose to participate in a survey, promotion, event or similar initiative.

* Information collected by automated means such as cookies or pixels. This may include information about your device and browser, including IP address, as well as information about how you and others use, interact with or respond to the Services. This collection may take place while you are using a Service or while the Service is running in the background of your device.

* Precise location information associated with your device when location services are active.

* Information we obtain from other sources, such as social media platforms.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

What Information We Obtain

* Information you provide when you use the Services, including when you sign up for communications, purchase products or services, create an account or register through the Services. This may include your contact, payment or demographic information.

* Information you submit when you choose to participate in a survey, promotion, event or similar initiative.

* Information collected by automated means such as cookies or pixels. This may include information about your device and browser, including IP address, as well as information about how you and others use, interact with or respond to the Services. This collection may take place while you are using a Service or while the Service is running in the background of your device.

* Precise location information associated with your device when location services are active.

* Information we obtain from other sources, such as social media platforms.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

###### How We Use Information We Obtain

* To process your requests and provide you with the Services, including enhancing the quality and your overall experience with the Services. Note that we use your payment card information (such as your card number and expiration date) for limited purposes such as to process your transaction (including recurring payments, if applicable), to provide you with the requested products or services and to protect our rights or the rights of others.

* To learn about users of the Services and analyze how you and others interact with and respond to the Services.

* To communicate with you, including to send you marketing and promotional communications.

* For advertising and marketing purposes, including to analyze the performance of advertising and marketing activities.

* To protect our rights and the rights of others.

* The use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the Chrome Web Store User Data Policy, including the Limited Use requirements.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

How We Use Information We Obtain

* To process your requests and provide you with the Services, including enhancing the quality and your overall experience with the Services. Note that we use your payment card information (such as your card number and expiration date) for limited purposes such as to process your transaction (including recurring payments, if applicable), to provide you with the requested products or services and to protect our rights or the rights of others.

* To learn about users of the Services and analyze how you and others interact with and respond to the Services.

* To communicate with you, including to send you marketing and promotional communications.

* For advertising and marketing purposes, including to analyze the performance of advertising and marketing activities.

* To protect our rights and the rights of others.

* The use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the Chrome Web Store User Data Policy, including the Limited Use requirements.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

###### How We Share Information

* With our affiliates and subsidiaries.

* With service providers that perform services or handle transactions on our behalf.

* With advertisers, advertising- and marketing-related services providers and partners as well as companies that help us learn how you and others interact with our Services.

* With social media platforms and similar services, including when you interact with our Services that integrate tools and services provided by social medial platforms.

* With business partners, such as when we partner with a third party to offer products or services on a co-branded basis.

* Other parties when required by law or as necessary to protect our rights, and in the context of corporate transactions.

* With your consent or otherwise at your direction.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

How We Share Information

* With our affiliates and subsidiaries.

* With service providers that perform services or handle transactions on our behalf.

* With advertisers, advertising- and marketing-related services providers and partners as well as companies that help us learn how you and others interact with our Services.

* With social media platforms and similar services, including when you interact with our Services that integrate tools and services provided by social medial platforms.

* With business partners, such as when we partner with a third party to offer products or services on a co-branded basis.

* Other parties when required by law or as necessary to protect our rights, and in the context of corporate transactions.

* With your consent or otherwise at your direction.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

###### Your Choices

* You may unsubscribe from our marketing or promotional emails by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link in our emails, or for certain Services, by logging into your account and adjusting your preferences.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

Your Choices

* You may unsubscribe from our marketing or promotional emails by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link in our emails, or for certain Services, by logging into your account and adjusting your preferences.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

###### Additional Information

* We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

* The Services are operated from the United States. Information may be processed and stored in the United States or other countries.

* The Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 13.

* This Privacy Policy is part of the applicable agreements which govern your use of the Services and any disputes related to your use of the Services (including our use of your information) will be resolved per the dispute resolution provision in such agreements.

* Additional disclosures and rights apply to California residents and European visitors. These are included at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

Additional Information

* We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

* The Services are operated from the United States. Information may be processed and stored in the United States or other countries.

* The Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 13.

* This Privacy Policy is part of the applicable agreements which govern your use of the Services and any disputes related to your use of the Services (including our use of your information) will be resolved per the dispute resolution provision in such agreements.

* Additional disclosures and rights apply to California residents and European visitors. These are included at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Read more in our full Privacy Policy below.

###### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@thehive.ai](mailto:privacy@thehive.ai). For questions related to your CCPA rights, please contact us by email at [ccpa-requests@thehive.ai](mailto:ccpa-requests@thehive.ai).  
  
You may also contact us via mail at Castle Global, Inc.,  
575 Market Street,  
15th Floor,  
San Francisco,  
CA 94105,  
Attn: Privacy.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@thehive.ai](mailto:privacy@thehive.ai). For questions related to your CCPA rights, please contact us by email at [ccpa-requests@thehive.ai](mailto:ccpa-requests@thehive.ai).  
  
You may also contact us via mail at Castle Global, Inc.,  
575 Market Street,  
15th Floor,  
San Francisco,  
CA 94105,  
Attn: Privacy.

#### Privacy Policy - Full

###### Our Policy

Our Policy

###### What Information We Obtain

What Information We Obtain

###### How We Use Information We Obtain

How We Use Information We Obtain

###### How We Share Information

How We Share Information

###### Your Choices

Your Choices

###### Security

Security

###### Non-U.S. Visitors and Users

Non-U.S. Visitors and Users

###### Children

Children

###### Links to Other Properties or Services

Links to Other Properties or Services

###### Careers/Job Opportunities

Careers/Job Opportunities

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Changes to this Privacy Policy

###### Exclusions

Exclusions

###### Other Terms and Conditions

Other Terms and Conditions

###### Contact Us

Contact Us

###### Additional Information for California Residents

Additional Information for California Residents

###### Additional Information for EEA Visitors

Additional Information for EEA Visitors

AI Models

Applications

Platform Solutions

Media Solutions

Company

Contact Us

[](https://thehive.ai/)© Copyright 2024

#### AI Models

#### Applications

#### Platform Solutions

#### Media Solutions

#### Company

#### Other Site Pages

[](https://thehive.ai/)© Copyright 2024
